[
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (10x + 6) + (6x + 10)?",
      "correctAnswer": "16x + 16",
      "options": [
        "15x + 16",
        "17x + 16",
        "16x + 17",
        "16x + 16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (5x + 1) + (1x + 5)?",
      "correctAnswer": "6x + 6",
      "options": [
        "6x + 7",
        "5x + 6",
        "6x + 6",
        "7x + 6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (1x + 5) + (5x + 1)?",
      "correctAnswer": "6x + 6",
      "options": [
        "5x + 6",
        "6x + 6",
        "7x + 6",
        "6x + 7"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (9x + 9) + (9x + 9)?",
      "correctAnswer": "18x + 18",
      "options": [
        "18x + 18",
        "19x + 18",
        "18x + 19",
        "17x + 18"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (9x + 7) + (7x + 9)?",
      "correctAnswer": "16x + 16",
      "options": [
        "16x + 17",
        "15x + 16",
        "16x + 16",
        "17x + 16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (8x + 7) + (7x + 8)?",
      "correctAnswer": "15x + 15",
      "options": [
        "15x + 15",
        "14x + 15",
        "16x + 15",
        "15x + 16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (10x + 9) + (9x + 10)?",
      "correctAnswer": "19x + 19",
      "options": [
        "18x + 19",
        "20x + 19",
        "19x + 20",
        "19x + 19"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (3x + 3) + (3x + 3)?",
      "correctAnswer": "6x + 6",
      "options": [
        "6x + 6",
        "5x + 6",
        "6x + 7",
        "7x + 6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (8x + 5) + (5x + 8)?",
      "correctAnswer": "13x + 13",
      "options": [
        "12x + 13",
        "13x + 14",
        "13x + 13",
        "14x + 13"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (8x + 8) + (8x + 8)?",
      "correctAnswer": "16x + 16",
      "options": [
        "17x + 16",
        "15x + 16",
        "16x + 17",
        "16x + 16"
      ]
    }
]